Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.06.20 15:40:51
记得我还是孩子时
As rough as I had it as a kid,
连圣诞节都会让我兴奋不已
even I got excited when Christmas came around.
Chris "揶菜"怎么拼?
Chris, how do you spell "cabbage"?
C-A-B-B-A-G-E
C-A-B-B-A-G-E.
谢谢 "揶菜娃娃" （一种大头娃娃）
Thanks. Cabbage Patch.
哦 Chris!
Oh, Chris!
瞧这山地车多酷
Look at this cool BMX bike.
哦 真挺酷
Oh, that's cool!
Chris 你礼物单上写什么了?
Chris, what are you putting on your list?
我才没写什么礼物单
I'm not writing a list.
那是给小孩子准备的
That's for kids.
我没写礼物单
I wasn't writing a list,
因为我唯一想要的
because the only thing I wanted
是便携式随身听
was a portable cassette player.
有了随身听你就可以听 那些污七八糟的音乐了
Having a Walkman meant you could even listen to bad music
而且还没人知道
and nobody had to know.
*喊 喊*
# Shout, #
*发泄出来*
# let it all out... #
除非你傻到自己唱出来
Unless you were dumb enough to sing along.
*我必须做 *
# ...I can do without #
*来吧 *
# Come on #
*我跟你说哪 *
# I'm talking to you, #
*来吧 *
# come on... #
我把随身听的广告丢的满屋都是
I had been leaving that ad all over the house,
所以我很确定老妈能得到暗示
so I was pretty sure my mother got the hint.
*在运动场等我 *
# Meet me in the playground #
*差一刻四点的时候 *
# At a quarter to 4:00 #
*直等到 *
# Wait till #
*所有人都走远 *
# everybody's long gone #
*也许会有些 *
# There might be some #
*事情我们可以表白 *
# things we could explore #
*嘿 宝贝 *
# Hey, baby, #
*也许我可以陪你走回家 *
# maybe I could walk you home... #
既然我只想要这一个礼物 我知道我肯定能得到
Since I only wanted one gift, I knew I'd get it.
这将会是史上最棒的一次圣诞节
This was going to be the best Christmas ever.
宽扎节快乐* (*美国黑人在新年前7天的节日) Kunta Kinte*(*冈比亚人 非洲的骄傲)
Happy Kwanza, Kunta Kinte.
好吧 也许不是史上最棒
Well, maybe not ever.
人人都恨克里斯 第一季   第11集 "人人都恨圣诞节"
1x11 - Everybody Hates Christmas
Transcript: Raceman - Adaptation: Sixe FOROM.COM
- 我能得到ColecoVision(游戏机) - 等等
- I'm getting a ColecoVision. - Wait.
你已经有了Atari(游戏机) 现在有有了ColecoVision(游戏机)?
You have an Atari and you're getting a ColecoVision?
耶 你得到什么礼物?
Yeah. What are you getting?
我将得到随身听
I'm getting a Walkman.
不可能吧
No way.
我要求的就这么一个东西
It's the only thing I've been asking for.
哥们 我真想来一个 你太幸运了
Man, I would kill for one of those. You're so lucky.
你爸怎不给你买一个?
How come your dad doesn't get you one?
审查制度
Censorship--
他必须确定能听到我听的音乐
he wants to makes sure he can hear the music I'm listening to.
开始说唱很有趣 后来说唱变武器
First rap was fun, then rap was gun.
放开我 婊子 废物 你们俩都是
Let me go, you bitches. You're punks, both of you.
西区! 西区!
West side! West side!
几年以后 Greg模仿了一下Ice Cube* (*美国黑人说唱歌手)
Years later, Greg played some Ice Cube
他的亲爸爸照着他就来了一枪
and his own father shot him.
全班注意
Class,
既然现在是给予的季节
since this is the season of giving,
我希望大家都能带些罐装食品
I'd like you all to bring in canned food items,
把它捐赠给那些不走运的人们
so we can donate them to those less fortunate.
有件很有趣的事 大多数人只在圣诞节
It's funny how most people only think
才想到捐赠物品给穷人
about feeding the needy during Christmas.
我相信总统日 那天也有很多挨饿的人
I'm sure there's a lot of hungry people during President's Day.
什么事 Chris?
Yes, Chris?
只能带罐装食品吗?
Do we have to bring in cans?
我们能不能带 比如 盒装食品?
Can we bring in, like, boxes of food?
你不用勉强带
You don't have to bring anything,
难为你这么有心了
but that's very thoughtful of you.
我知道一年中的这时候 你家肯定很困难
I know this time of year must be hard for your family.
不 我们挺好的
No. We're doing fine.
我了解
I know.
在她眼里好像那晚我们全家 只能一人一碗西北风一样
She made it seem like we were having a bowl of steam for dinner that night.
谁把热水都用光了?
Who used up all the hot water?
外面只有5度
It's five degrees outside.
想把我冻死吗?
What you trying to do, kill me?
Chris之前洗了个澡也说水凉
Chris said it was cool when he took a shower earlier.
哦!
Oh!
也许是热水器又坏了
The hot water heater's probably broken again.
你能修好吗?
You think you can fix it?
我已经用胶带和弹簧把他们绑在一起了
I'm already holding it together with duct tape and hangers.
看来我们只能换一个了
We're just gonna have to replace it.
那 宝贝 要花多少钱啊?
Well, baby, how much to you think that's gonna cost?
比手头儿的多
More than I got.
那 我们还够钱买圣诞礼物吗?
Well, will we still have enough money to but Christmas presents?
我以为你都买完了
I thought you finished shopping.
嗯 我给Drew和Tonya买了一些
Well, I bought a few things for Drew and Tonya,
但我还要给Chris买个随身听
but I have got to get that Walkman for Chris.
从感恩节开始 他就不断给我提示和线索了
he's been giving me hints and clues since Thanksgiving.
天 孩子们圣诞节要的礼物太多了
Man, these kids get too many gifts on Christmas.
当我还是个孩子的时候 不是买礼物
When I was a kid, instead of buying gifts,
而是我老爸把警察叫到家里
my father used to call the cops on Christmas
告诉我们家里被劫了
and tell us the house got robbed.
为了赚到额外的钱过圣诞节
In order to make extra money for Christmas,
我老爸什么活儿都接
my father would do any job.
一共是30块
That'll be $30.
当出租车司机
He worked as a cab driver.
没什么的
That's okay.
打个零工赚些额外钱 对他再简单不过了
It  was easy for him to pick up odd jobs
当他需要的时候
for extra money when he needed it.
圣诞节快乐
Merry Christmas.
- 滚一下毛吗 先生? - 好吧
- Lint roll, sir? - Yeah.
当滚毛人
He worked as a lint roller.
谢谢
Thank you.
他甚至干过尝机油的活儿
He even worked as an oil taster.
这是10W30型机油
This is 10-W 30.
你需要10W40
You need 10-W 40.
这才是父亲
Now that's a father.
Drew
Drew.
- Drew - 噢
- Drew! - Ow!
你干嘛打我?
What'd you do that for?
你怎么拼"Malibu"(雪佛兰一款车)
How do you spell "Malibu."
M-A-L-I-BOO? (boo:嘘)
M-A-L-I-BOO?
你还在写那白痴的圣诞礼单吗?
Are  you still writing that stupid Christmas list?
才不白痴呢
It's not stupid.
不 就是白痴
Yes, it is.
人人都知道没有圣诞老人 Tonya.
Everybody knows there's no Santa Claus, Tonya.
那不是事实
That's not true.
也不是白痴的
And it's not stupid.
- 你才是白痴 - 你是白痴
- You're stupid. - You're stupid.
你是白痴
You're stupid.
Drew 别再叫你妹妹白痴了!
Drew, stop calling your sister stupid!
我老妈有双千里耳
My mother had amazing hearing.
我们在家里做什么她都听的到
We couldn't do anything in our house without her hearing it.
Chris!别把棉球扔的哪儿都是!
Chris! Quit throwing cotton balls all over the place!
你们吵什么那?
Now what are y'all arguing about?
没什么
Nothing.
Drew说根本没有圣诞老人这么回事
Drew said there's no such thing as Santa Claus.
你胡说什么那 孩子?
What are you talking about, boy?
当然有圣诞老人了 宝贝
Of course there's a Santa Claus, baby.
- 嘿 你好吗Drew? - 嘿
- Hey. What's up Drew? - Hey.
妈妈 学校有个捐罐头活动
Mama, we're having a food drive at school.
我能拿几个罐头吗?
Can I bring some canned goods?
可以 但别拿那些杂牌儿的
Okay. But don't take generic brands.
那些名牌儿的
Only store brands.
我不想让那些人觉得我们捐不起
I do not want those people thinking we can't afford to donate food.
我老妈可以把我们 所有的食物送出去
My mother would give away all the food we had if she
如果她觉得这样 可以证明我们衣食无缺
thought it would prove we didn't need it.
你为什么说我的礼物单白痴?
How come you say my list is stupid?
因为 每个人都知道没圣诞老人
Because, everybody knows there's no Santa Claus.
过来 我给你看点东西
Come here, let me show you something.
我们这是去哪儿?
Where are we going?
我带你去看玩具
I'm taking you to the toys.
没有圣诞老人烟囱里进来
Santa doesn't come down the chimney.
我们甚至都没烟囱 只有散热器
We don't even have a chimney, we have radiators.
你听说过有圣诞老人 从散热器里进来吗?
Have you ever heard of Santa Claus coming through radiators?
可是我们的玩具怎么可能准备好呢 我的礼物单都没写完呢
But how can we have our toys already if I haven't even finished my list?
因为...
Because.
嘿 儿子
Hey, man.
在干嘛?
What you doing?
把罐头带到学校给穷人
I'm taking canned goods to school for the needy.
儿子 这些罐头总价2块8毛9呢
Man, that's $2.89 cent worth of food.
你在想什么那
What you trying to do,
救穷人还是当穷人?
feed the needy or be the needy?
- Rochelle! - Julius!
“我就挣那么点钱”
“你怎么还想法乱花”
My parents tried not argue in front of the kids,
“我不想让人觉得我们破产了” 我父母不想在孩子面前吵架
“我不想让人觉得我们破产了” 所以他们就用脸色交流
so instead, they just made faces.
我们马上破产！
但他们不必知道！
他们还能用脸诅咒彼此
They make curse out faces, too,
但不能给你们看
but we can't show you those.
与此同时 Drew在给Tanya 看一些孩子不该看的东西
Meanwhile, Drew was showing Tanya something no kid should see.
看到没 告诉过你了
See, I told you.
哇噢! 酷!
Whoa! Cool!
有糟糕一天的不止是Tonya
Tonya wasn't the only one having a bad day.
有什么问题吗?
Is there something wrong?
坐下来 宝贝
Have a seat, baby.
上一次他们让我坐下来 是听他们宣布
The last time they asked me to sit down before they told me something,
杰克逊五人组*解散的消息 (*MJ小时候和兄弟们组的乐队)
The Jackson Five broke up.
嘿 Chris
Hey, Chris.
呃 宝贝 听着 我知道你早就盼着
Um, baby, look, I know you've been looking forward to getting
圣诞节能得到随身听了
that new Walkman for Christmas.
还有 Chris 我一直希望我的孩子
And, Chris, I've always wanted my kids
能比我小时候圣诞节过的好
to have a better Christmas than I had growing up.
但你越长大
But the older you get,
所要做的牺牲也就越多
the more you learn about the sacrifices you have to make.
牺牲?
Sacrifices?
呃...
Uh...
比如不能买新的工作靴 这样你的孩子就能有鞋穿
Like not getting a new pair of work boots so you kids can have shoes.
再比如你乘地铁去上班 这样你老婆就能有车开
Or like taking the subway to work so your wife can use the car.
“我说我会给你买车的！”
“我说什么了”
妈妈 爸爸 我13岁了
Mom, Dad, I'm 13.
那 你圣诞节收不到礼物了
Well, you're not getting a present for Christmas.
他说这个时 就好像我们培根吃光了
He said that like we're out of bacon.
我们必须要买个新热水器
We got to buy a new water heater.
好吧 那我们得想想怎么 告诉Drew和Tonya
Well, then, we need a plan to tell Drew and Tonya.
告诉他们什么?
Tell them what?
圣诞节得不到任何礼物啊
That they're not getting any presents for Christmas.
谁说他们圣诞节得不到礼物了?
Who said they weren't getting anything for Christmas?
等等 他们有东西拿我没有?
Wait, they're getting stuff and I'm not?
你比他们大 Chris
You're older, Chris.
他们不理解
They wouldn't understand.
我什么都没有吗?
Am I gonna get anything?
哦 宝贝 热水你想用多少就用多少
Oh, baby, you'll be able to use up all the hot water you want.
这么说我得到的 就只是干净屁股了?
So all I'm getting is a clean ass?
热气腾腾哦
Steaming hot.
# 人人都恨克里斯 #
#  Everybody hates Chris. #
这么说圣诞节你什么都得不到了?
So you're not getting anything for Christmas?
是滴
Nope.
哥们 圣诞节没礼物?
Man, nothing for Christmas?
这算不算虐待儿童啊?
Isn't that considered child abuse?
确实有这种感觉
Sure does feel like it.
至少他们会在你袜子里放些什么吧?
They're at least gonna put something in your stocking, right?
可能是根剩香肠什么的吧
Maybe some leftover sausage.
应该立法来阻止此类事发生
There's got to be a law against this.
哦 Chris 看看你
Oh, Chris, look at you.
你不用带食物来的
You didn't have to bring any food.
有时我忘了你们的人民有多坚强
Sometimes I forget how strong your people are.
你说我们的人民有多坚强 是什么意思?
What  do you mean how strong my people are?
"我说你们的人民有多坚强 是什么意思"?
"What do I mean how strong your people are?"
总有一天你会明白的
You shall overcome someday.
下课后来找我
See me after class.
我有东西送给你
I have something for you.
Ok
Okay.
我们会明白的
We shall overcome
我们会
We shall
明白的...
overcome...
Tonya 我以为你在挂装饰物呢
Tonya, I thought you were gonna put up the decorations.
我现在不太想
I don't want to now.
为什么呀?
Why not?
因为 你和爹的骗我
Because... you and Daddy lied to me.
我们骗你? 什么啊?
We lied to you? About what?
我知道没有圣诞老人这回事
I know there's no such thing as Santa Claus.
当我老妈听到 Tonya说出这几个字
When my mother heard Tonya say those words,
就好像Tonya不再是 她的宝贝女儿一样
it was like she wasn't her baby anymore.
那你们还想骗我什么?
So what else to you lie to me about?
我要怀孕了你们真把我赶出去吗?
Are you really gonna kick me out if I get pregnant?
你说你不养孩子是真的吗?
Is it true you ain't taking care of no baby?
我真不能带白人男孩回家吗?
Can I really not bring a white boy home?
烤炉食品真能让人发胖吗?
Does the Foreman Grill really knock out the fat?
没有资金来源我真能贷款吗?
Can I really get a loan with no money down?
你是我亲妈吗?
Are you my real mother?
妈妈 我要答案
Momma, I want answers.
Tonya 和妈妈跟你说过的一样
Tonya, like Mommy told you,
有圣诞老人的存在
there is a Santa Claus.
那为什么楼上的房间里 堆满了礼物?
So how come there's a room upstairs full of presents?
谁告诉你的?
Who told you that?
Drew带我去看的
Drew showed me.
Drew 给我过来!
Drew, get in here!
啥事 妈妈?
Yes, Mom?
你带Tonya上楼看礼物了?
Did you show Tonya the presents upstairs?
对呀
Yeah.
我们得聊聊
We need to talk.
呃...呃...不
Uh... uh... no.
等等 妈妈 不 不
Hold  on, Momma. No, no.
我老妈整天都喊着要揍我们
My mother talked about beating us all the time,
但她真正要揍我们 只是在她说要"聊聊"的时候
but the only time she ever beat us is when she said she wanted to talk.
那一晚她把Drew聊了个底儿掉
And she talked the hell out of Drew that night.
哦不错嘛 这些是什么东西?
Oh... well, what's all this stuff?
从我老师那儿得到的
I got it from  my teacher.
她觉得我们是处在 下层社会 饥饿状态
She thinks that we're underprivileged and starving.
哦 不
Oh, no.
嗯嗯
Mm-mmm.
绝对不行
Absolutely not.
我绝对不能 让那些人认为我们没的吃
I'm not going to have them people thinking that we don't have anything to eat.
她还没有尊严到 把那些橄榄放回去
She wasn't too proud to take those olives.
你去哪?
Where you going?
我去往这里再装点吃的
I'm taking this to put some more food in it,
明天你把它带回学校去
'cause you're taking this back to school tomorrow.
我老妈很生气有人 认为我们需要施舍
My mother was so upset about people thinking we needed charity,
这使她几乎忘了没给我礼物 带来的罪恶感
she almost forgot she felt guilty about not getting me a gift.
Chris 稍等片刻
Chris, wait a minute.
听着 我很抱歉
Look... I'm sorry.
我知道这些不是你的错
I know all of this is not your fault.
还知道这让我看起来像有病一样
And I know it seems kind of crazy with me giving back
当我们买不起你的圣诞礼物时 还把免费食物送回去
free food when we can't even afford to buy you a Christmas gift.
没什么
It's okay.
后来 我老妈给了我 一件她买的起的礼物
After that, my mother gave me the one gift she could afford--
她对我真的很好
she was really nice to me!
当你最疯狂的梦想成真时 谁还需要圣诞节?
Who needs Christmas when all your wildest dreams come true?
Chris吃大块儿的
Chris gets the big piece.
我吃到了大块鸡
I got the big piece of chicken.
圣诞节快乐
Merry Christmas.
我不用干任何家务活
I didn't have to do any chores.
Tonya 刷盘子
Tonya, wash the dishes.
我以为是Chris刷
I thought Chris had to do 'em.
你以为错了
You thought wrong.
我让Tonya陷入麻烦
I got Tonya in trouble.
嗷!嗷!
Ow! Ow!
妈妈 Tonya打了我两下
Mama, Tonya hit me twice.
感觉真好 我不由在想
It felt so good, I was thinking
要是我永远得不到礼物 生活会变成什么样子
what life would be like if I never got a present.
起来 让你哥看电视
Get up and let your brother watch TV.
- 可是妈妈... - 可是个屁!起来
- But Mom? - But nothing! Get up.
我在想要是房顶塌下来 我能得到什么
I wondered what I could get if the roof caved in.
亲下!
Mwa!
嘿 Drew 把遥控器递过来?
Hey, Drew, can you pass me the remote?
好 行
Yeah, right.
妈...
Ma...
我不敢相信日子会这么好
I couldn't believe how good I had it.
同时 Tonya不相信任何事
Meanwhile, Tonya didn't believe anything.
妈妈 玉米面包是玉米做的吗?
Mama, is cornbread made of corn?
啊...不是
Hmm... no.
应该是玉米粉做的 怎么问这个?
I think it's made of cornmeal. Why?
随便问问
Just checking.
怎么你想让圣诞老人送你玉米面包?
Why, you want Santa Claus to bring you some cornbread for Christmas?
耶 他能连揶菜娃娃给你一块带来
Yeah, he could bring it with your Cabbage Patch Doll.
嘿 嘿 别说了
Hey, hey. Stop it.
Ok? 够了啊
Okay? Enough.
放过你们妹妹吧
Leave your sister alone.
Drew 你相信“复活节兔子” 在Tonya这么大时候
Drew, you believed in the Easter Bunny till you was about her age, and Chris,
Chris你呢 差点弄掉所有牙
you damn near lost all your teeth before
直到你不相信"牙仙"
you stopped believing in the Tooth Fairy.
连复活节兔子和牙仙也不存在?
There's no Easter Bunny or Tooth Fairy, either?
呃...
Uh...
不 宝贝 他 他 他不是这意思
No, baby, he-he-he didn't mean that.
最好有人把牙还我
Somebody better give me my teeth back.
宝贝 我不是这意思!
Baby, I didn't mean it!
我不是这意思!
I didn't mean it!
Julius!
我要我的牙!
I want my teeth back!
宝贝 不...
Baby, no...
- Tonya! - 我们在开玩笑!
- Tonya! - We were joking!
那是个玩笑!
It's a joke!
是个...
It's a...
是个玩笑!
It's a joke!
就是她 她说圣诞老人不来咱家
That's her. She said Santa can't come to our house,
因为我们有的只是暖炉
'cause all we have is space heaters.
而圣诞老人不会从暖炉下来
And Santa can't come through a space heater.
你怎么养孩子的?
What kind of children are you raising?
这孩子满城跑 破坏别人美梦
This girl's going around town crushing dreams.
- 我... - 是你教她这样的吗?
- I... - Is that what you want her to be?
- 破坏美梦者? - 不是 可你...!
- A dream crusher? - No, but you...!
得管管这孩子
That girl needs to be stopped.
Tonya!
这是事实!
It's the truth!
通常情况下 我妈会把Tonya打得头发出油
Normally, my mama would smack the grease out of Tonya's hair.
但老妈不能因为讲真话打她
But she couldn't smack her for telling the truth.
那是什么?
What's that?
我妈让我把这些东西拎回来
My mom made me bring all this stuff back.
证明我们有能力捐食物
It proves that we can afford to donate food.
嘿 看看 我有东西送你
Hey, look... I got something for you.
谢谢
Thanks!
- 是什么? - 把它打开
- What's this? - Open it.
"电脑游戏"（歌曲专辑）
"Computer Games."
- 谁的歌? - George Clinton (黑人老歌手 发型怪异)
- Who is it? - George Clinton.
里面有首歌 "电子狗"
There's a song on there, "Atomic Dog",
我在广播里听过 很有趣的
I heard on the radio. It's really funny.
- 你觉得我会喜欢? - 不知道
- You think I'll like it? - I don't know.
有一天你得到你的随身听时 至少你会有一盘磁带
When you finally do get your Walkman, at least you'll have a tape.
我一直很欣赏 Greg的乐观精神
I always liked that Greg was so optimistic.
时至今日 他还是认为 Al B.Sure(歌手)会重返乐坛
To this day, he still thinks Al B. Sure's gonna make a comeback.
可如果圣诞老人不存在
But if Santa Claus is not real,
为什么人们要编造一个呢?
why do people make it up?
Tonya 圣诞老人只是一种方式 来教导孩子懂得给予
Tonya, Santa is just a way to teach kids about the spirit of giving.
他只是一种 象征 仅此而已
He's just a... symbol, that's all.
哦
Oh.
Tonya
Tonya...
你是大姑娘了 到了了解真相的岁数
you're a big girl, and, now that you're old enough to know
为别的孩子不破坏这个秘密 是你的责任 好吗?
the truth, it's your responsibility to not spoil it for other kids, okay?
因为你想给他们一些东西来信仰
Because you want to give them something to believe in.
完全正确
Exactly.
这才是我的好闺女
That's my big girl.
亲下
Mwa!
那 你真理解了吧
So, you do understand.
对 撒谎没问题
Yeah. It's okay to lie.
晚安 妈妈
Good night, Mommy.
你觉得向Tonya 解释圣诞老人很困难
You think explaining Santa Claus to Tonya was hard,
那你真该看看 跟她解释两性关系时的状况
you should have been there for the birds and the bees.
呦 真恶心!
Eww... that's nasty!
圣诞节前夕似乎无人睡眠
Nobody  ever seems to get any sleep on Christmas Eve.
每个人都因为不同原因醒着
Everybody's up for different reasons.
你干什么 宝贝?
What you doing, baby?
准备牛奶和饼干
Setting out milk and cookies.
我们聊过这些了
We talked about this.
是聊过 但这不是为圣诞老人准备的
We did... and they're not for Santa.
是给您的
They're for you.
谢谢 宝贝
Thank you, baby.
但既然知道我什么礼物都没有
But since I wasn't getting anything,
我就没这些问题了
I didn't have that problem.
圣诞节的早上 我甚至把时间花在下楼上
On Christmas morning, I even took my time going downstairs.
现在Tonya知道了没有圣诞老人
Now that Tonya knew there wasn't a Santa Claus,
她的抱怨直冲着老妈就来了
her complaints went directly to my mother.
妈妈 我要的是长发的揶菜娃娃
Mama, I wanted a Cabbage Patch Doll with long hair.
给你来个没头发的空气娃娃怎么样?
How about you have no doll with no hair?
哦 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
Ok
Okay.
Chris 这是给你的 宝贝
Chris, this one is for you, baby.
- 是新唱片吗? - 打开自己看
- Is it a new album? - Open it and find out.
有家医院正在派发这东西 我往那儿送报纸
They were giving those away at the doctor's office I deliver papers to.
我觉得你在学校也许用的上
I thought you could use it for school.
谢谢 我会用的
Thanks. I will.
嘿 Chris 你得到什么?
Hey, Chris, what'd you get?
一本日历
A calendar.
日历?
A calendar?
耶 这就是我想要的
Yeah, that's what I wanted.
看看 看这个
See, now, look here.
你知道五月是高血压发病高峰吗?
Did you know that May is High Blood Pressure Month?
不知
No.
除非你们有这日历?
What if you had a calendar?
看到没?
See?
明年你们全都得要日历
All y'all should ask for calendars next year.
好主意
That's a good idea.
嘿 Chris待会想和我出去骑车吗?
Hey, Chris, you want to go ride my bike with me outside later?
他说的"待会" 指的是夏天
By "later," he meant summer.
耶 当然
Yeah, sure.
嘿 Chris
Hey, Chris...
这个可以给你
you can have this.
你确定?
You sure?
对 我确定
Yeah. I'm sure.
宝贝 这样真好
Baby, that's nice.
我也这么以为的
That's what I thought, too.
耶! 我又赢啦!
Yes! I won again!
赢死你! 呜!
In your face! Ooh!
又怎样? 新年也没礼物?
What now? I don't get New Year's?
亲下!
Mwa!
- 谢谢 - 谢什么?
- Thank you. - For what?
你没得到你想要东西的处理方式
For the way you've handled not getting what you wanted.
你真的让我们感到骄傲 儿子
You've really made us proud, man.
Drew和Tonya还是孩子
Drew and Tonya are kids.
他们比我更需要圣诞礼物
They need Christmas presents more than me.
知道吗 你真的长大了 Chris.
You know, you're really growing up, Chris.
家里又多了个男子汉感觉真好
It's kind of nice having another man around the house.
说来奇怪
It was weird.
那天早上父母给我的感受
That morning with my parents felt better
比我收到过的任何礼物都好
than any gift I ever got.
给你这个
Here you go.
这是什么?
What's this?
玩具店优惠券
Toy store coupon.
打5折
50% off.
三月之前都能用
It's good till March.
那一天快结束的时候
By the end of the day,
我没有礼物再不是 什么大不了的事了
it didn't even matter anymore that I didn't have a gift,
因为我拥有了美好的一天
because I had a good day.
好了现在 我们来采访 Vivian Morello女士
And right now, I'm with Mrs. Vivian Morello.
- 嘿 那是我老师 - 你今晚有什么安排?
- Hey, that's my teacher. - And what are you doing tonight?
每年 我的学生都会收集食物 为那些最可怜的
Every year, my students collect food for the very poorest,
最缺少温暖的 最贫困的家庭
most destitute and neediest families.
那些人太可怜了
These people are so poor,
他们也许除了背上披的 衣服以外就一无所有了
they probably don't have anything but the clothes on their backs.
即使他们很尴尬的处于社会底层
Even though they're embarrassingly underprivileged,
自尊心不允许他们寻求帮助
they're just too proud to ask for help.
Too proud to ask for help.
而且他们很穷
And they're poor.
而今晚 我们将给予一个家庭 这一篮物品
And tonight, we're going to give a family this basket.
有谁愿意在电视上看到被敲门
Now, who wants somebody coming to their door on TV
说出他们有多贫穷啊?
talking about how poor they are?
好兴奋
So exciting.
嗯 我去开门
Hmm, I'll get it.
准备好了吗
You got it?
圣诞快乐! 圣诞快乐!
Merry Christmas! Merry Christmas!
Chris!
人人都恨克里斯
Everybody hates Chris...